singlepoint.com 2009-12-14

# SinglePoint - Engage Your Consumers Through Mobile

## Effective Date: November 3, 2006

This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to www.goingsinglepoint.com (the "Site"), which is owned and operated by Wireless Services Corporation and its affiliates (collectively "WSC") and to WSC's mobile applications and related services (collectively, and together with the Site, the "Services"). This Policy does not apply to information collected "offline" or not related to the WSC Services. In particular, this Policy does not apply to information collected by WSC as an agent for any third party service provider or cellular phone company.

## Modifications of this Policy

WSC reserves the right to change this Policy at any time without notice and by using this Site or the Services subsequent to any revision of the Policy, you agree to be bound by such changes. Please note that we will post any changes to this Policy on this Site, and other places we deem appropriate so that our users may make themselves aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it and to whom. We will use any information collected in accordance with the privacy policy in place at the time the information was collected. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy and familiarize yourself with the most current version.

## Information We Collect

Except in the limited circumstances provided below, we do not collect any personally identifiable information while you use the Services. Any personally identifiable information you provide is voluntary. The cases in which we do collect personally identifiable information are as follows:

## Registration and Use of the Services

You may be asked to open an account or complete a registration with WSC to download or purchase certain Services, including mobile applications Services. Information gathered during the registration or account creation process, or during access to particular products and services, may differ based on the nature of the product or service. Information that you provide when registering or creating an account, or accessing or using your account or the Services associated with your account, may include: name; phone number, email address; billing information; information concerning software downloaded, products and content purchased, accessed, downloaded and/or burned through Services; location information (such as zip code or postal code and country); computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); the IP Internet (IP) address and URL of the Website that sent you to the WSC registration page; demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, content preferences and personalization information); and whether you logged into or out of a Service, or changed your password or billing information. We may also collect and use certain types of non-personally identifiable information.

## Potential Customers

You may request information about SinglePoint or the Services on the Site. We will ask you for contact information including your name, your company's name, address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address.

## Information Collected From Other Sources

We may combine the information you provide with other information obtained from you or third parties to more effectively provide you with our services.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information while using the Services. WSC may use a persistent cookie for the Services. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

WSC may use cookies to create profiles of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on non-specific users, which details user preferences. We use this profile to tailor each user's interaction with the Services and to personalize our Services to your particular interests. 

This Policy covers the use of cookies by WSC only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers that may advertise through the Services. 

## Enhancement of Marketing Profile

We may purchase or otherwise receive third party marketing data and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide offers we think our users would be interested in. We may use this information to enhance the existing user profiles. This aggregate marketing data is tied to your user profile and used to tailor your interaction with the Services.

## Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use log files in connection with the Site. This includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, handset type, Internet service provider (ISP), platform type, and date/time stamp. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information about you. We collect and use this information in aggregate to tailor our services and to share with advertisers.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information we collect to effectively provide you with our services or to assist us in carrying our business objectives. We may disclose such information to third parties for such purposes.

## Children

We may require you to provide your age and date of birth in order to ensure compliance with U.S. government restrictions on web sites providing content to, and acquiring information from, children.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. WSC does not encourage children to use the Services or provide us with their personal information. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) ("COPPA"), we do not collect or maintain personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under the age of 13.

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

WSC may share personally identifiable information with our partners that provide us with content and technology, cellular service providers, our agents, representatives, and contractors in order to provide the Services. By using a mobile application Service you consent to our sharing of your personally identifiable information with third parties in connection with delivering such Services, including, without limitation your wireless service provider and WSC's content providers. Such third party's use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information is not governed by this Policy, and WSC may not cause the take down or modification of any information once conveyed to such parties. In addition, WSC may share aggregate statistical information about our users, traffic patterns, and related use information with third-party associates and vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

## Business Transition

In the event that WSC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sells a portion of its assets, users' information, in most instances, be a part of the assets transferred. Such a transfer shall not be considered a violation of or deviation from this Policy.

## Links to Third Party Sites and Services

WSC is not responsible for the privacy policies of websites and services to which the Services link, or of which the Services are a part (e.g. where the Services are part of the total services offered by your wireless service provider). If you provide any information to such third parties different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. We strongly suggest you review such third party's privacy policies before providing any data to them.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent loss, destruction, unauthorized access or alteration, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the Services, and the Services and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Users of the Services do so at their own risk.

## Disclosure Required by Law

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with applicable laws and regulations or to comply with legal process served on our Site.

## How to Contact Us

Please forward any complaints, questions or concerns to us at:

## SinglePoint   
600 108th Avenue NE   
Suite 610   
Bellevue, WA 98004
